### Contact

San Antonio Tx 2107797294 (Mobile) jldelbosque@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jamie-del-bosque-12718399 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
Wound Vac
Wound Care
Direct Patient Care

# Jamie Del Bosque

Travel Nurse at Continuum Medical Staffing

San Antonio, Texas Area

# Summary

Compassionate & dedicated Medical Professional with 12 years total LVN experience, in skilled nursing facilities, acute care, and currently home health settings, 4 years for pediatric private duty nursing. Trach/vent experience. Dependable and keen to details with in-depth knowledge of professional nursing principles and techniques and medical subjects, capable of managing heavy daily patient volume and still able to provide reliable care to patients. Professional, personable, with effective customer service and communication skills, adept at building productive relationships while building rapport with patients, staff, & individuals at any level or background.

# Experience

Continuum Medical Staffing Travel Nurse August 2019 - Present (11 months)

Fredericksburg, Texas

Epic Health Services, Inc.

LVN

September 2015 - Present (4 years 10 months)

San Antonio, TX

Pediatric home health LVN. Care of special needs children.

Medication administration, vital sign assessments, g tube management ,trach/vent certified

Contacting physicians and family with updates or changes in conditions, followed by documentation.

Noting changes in medication and treatments.

Used research based theory to assist physician in determining the reason for changes in clients condition.

Evaluated nursing intervention outcomes, conferring with other health care team members as necessary.

Able to perform basic physical assessments of pediatric patients.

### JONSAN HOME HEALTH INC

Home Health Licensed Practical Nurse July 2018 - February 2020 (1 year 8 months)

San Antonio, Texas, United States

Field nurse

Wound vac, trach, Plurex drains, picc management

### **CHRISTUS Health**

LVN

September 2016 - June 2017 (10 months)

San Antonio, Texas Area

#### Restorative Health Care

Pediatric Nurse

November 2014 - April 2017 (2 years 6 months)

San Antonio, Texas Area

Contacting physicians and family with updates or changes in conditions, followed by documentation.

Trach/vent certified.

Noting changes in medication and treatments.

Used research based theory to assist physician in determining the reason for changes in clients condition.

administer medications,

Evaluated nursing intervention outcomes, conferring with other health care team members as necessary

Able to perform basic physical assessments of pediatric patients.

Angels of Care Pediatric Home Health

Pediatric Nurse

July 2014 - December 2015 (1 year 6 months)

Devine, Texas

Care of special needs foster children. Medication administration, vital sign assessments, g tube management,trach/vent certified contacting physicians and family with updates or changes in conditions, followed by documentation. Noting changes in medication and treatments.

Used research based theory to assist physician in determining the reason for changes in clients condition.

Evaluated nursing intervention outcomes, conferring with other health care team members as necessary

Able to perform basic physical assessments of pediatric patients.

Epic Health Services, Inc.
Pediatric Nurse
June 2014 - November 2014 (6 months)

San Antonio, Texas Area

Pediatric home health LVN. Care of special needs foster children. Medication administration, vital sign assessments, g tube management,trach/vent certified Contacting physicians and family with updates or changes in conditions, followed by documentation.

Noting changes in medication and treatments.

Used research based theory to assist physician in determining the reason for changes in clients condition.

Wound Care- Assessing patient body and skin, initiating treatments for new skin conditions, continuing and enforcing skin treatments, caring and treating varieties of ulcers, preventing bed sores.

administer medications,

Diabetic management for geriatric patients in an in home setting.

Evaluated nursing intervention outcomes, conferring with other health care team members as necessary

Able to perform basic physical assessments of adult and pediatric patients.

#### Southern Texas Home Health

LVN

November 2010 - October 2014 (4 years)

Devine, Texas

Appointments required focused assessments, wound care, education and teaching.

Contacting physicians and family with updates or changes in conditions, followed by documentation.

Noting changes in medication and treatments.

Used research based theory to assist physician in determining the reason for changes in clients condition.

Provided care to elderly patients in a home setting with a wide range of terminal and non terminal illness. Wound Care- Assessing patient body and skin, initiating treatments for new skin conditions, continuing and enforcing skin treatments, caring and treating varieties of ulcers, preventing bed sores.

administer medications,

Diabetic management for geriatric patients in an in home setting.

Evaluated nursing intervention outcomes, conferring with other health care team members as necessary

Able to perform basic physical assessments of adult patients.

G-Tube medication administration, care and feeding

PICC line administration care and cleaning.

Documented all elements of nursing assessment, treatments, medications, discharge instructions and follow-up care

## BrightStar HealthCare San Antonio

LVN

June 2013 - December 2013 (7 months)

Contacting physicians and family with updates or changes in conditions, followed by documentation.

Noting changes in medication and treatments.

Used research based theory to assist physician in determining the reason for changes in clients condition.

Wound Care- Assessing patient body and skin, initiating treatments for new skin conditions, continuing and enforcing skin treatments, caring and treating varieties of ulcers, preventing bed sores.

administer medications.

Diabetic management for geriatric patients in an in home setting.

Evaluated nursing intervention outcomes, conferring with other health care team members as necessary

Able to perform basic physical assessments of adult and pediatric patients.

### Cameron Nursing Center

LVN Charge Nurse

August 2008 - October 2010 (2 years 3 months)

Provided care to elderly patients in a nursing home facility with a wide range of terminal illness.

Supervised up to 5 medical staff per shift

Documented all elements of nursing assessment, treatments, medications, discharge instructions and follow-up care

Wound Care- Assessing patient body and skin, initiating treatments for new skin conditions, continuing and enforcing skin treatments, caring and treating varieties of ulcers, preventing bed sores.

administer medications,

Diabetic management for geriatric patients in nursing care facilities.

Evaluated nursing intervention outcomes, conferring with other health care team members as necessary

Able to perform basic physical assessments of adult patients.

G-Tube medication administration, care and feeding

#### Scott & White Healthcare

LVN

May 2008 - January 2009 (9 months)

Provided care to trauma patients in a busy hospital setting with a wide range of injuries.

Documented all elements of nursing assessment, treatments, medications, discharge instructions and follow-up care

Wound Care- Assessing patient body and skin, initiating treatments for new skin conditions, continuing and enforcing skin treatments, caring and treating varieties of ulcers, preventing bed sores.

Diabetic management for patients in hospital setting

Evaluated nursing intervention outcomes, conferring with other health care team members as necessary

Able to perform basic physical assessments of adult patients.

G-Tube medication administration, care and feeding.

Proficient at foley catheter changing and care.

# Education

Galen College of Nursing-San Antonio

Associate's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2016 - 2020)

#### Temple College

Certificate of Completion, Licensed Practical/Vocational Nurse Training · (2007 - 2008)

Palo Alto College

AAS, Psychology · (2003 - 2006)